<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GogoZoo</string>
    <string name="home">MAP</string>
    <string name="list">LIST</string>
    <string name="schedule">SCHEDULE</string>
    <string name="person">PERSON</string>

    <style name="LoginDialog">
        <item name="android:windowBackground">@color/translucent_40</item>
    </style>

    <!-- Permissions -->
    <string name="permission_rationale_location">Access to the location service is required to demonstrate the \'my location\' feature, which shows your current location on the map.</string>
    <string name="location_permission_denied">This sample requires location permission to enable the \'my location\' layer. Please try again and grant access to use the location.\nIf the permission has been permanently denied, it can be enabled from the System Settings &gt; Apps &gt; \'Google Maps API Demos\'.</string>
    <string name="permission_required_toast">Location permission is required for this demo.</string>
    <string name="base_url">https://maps.googleapis.com</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="internet_not_connected">您尚未連接 Internet</string>
    <string name="you_know_nothing">You know nothing</string>

    <string name="area_detail">鳥園區包括鳥類形態區、雉類與珍禽區、鶴園、鸚鵡房、生態鳥園及水禽區，可以觀察到住在不同棲息地的鳥類，是都會環境中難得的賞鳥據點。歡迎放慢腳步，聽聽悅耳鳥鳴、看看羽色繽紛的輕盈身影，感受另一個廣闊而自由的世界。</string>

    <string name="animal_inter">赫曼氏陸龜 Hermann’s tortoise\n．特徵：體型小型，背甲高聳呈圓拱形，有兩個尾上盾片，後腳無棘刺突起，尾巴末端有一大型角質鱗片。背甲為黃褐色或深褐色，每一盾板上都有黑色的斑紋，腹甲為暗褐色或黑色，邊緣和中線為黃色。\nCharacteristics: It is a small tortoise with a high-domed carapace that is arched and rounded. It does not have any spurs projecting from the thighs, but does have two bony plates on the tail, and a large patch of horny scutes at the tip of the tail. The carapace is yellowish brown or dark brown in color. There are black markings on every scute. The plastron is dark brown or black, with both the rim and central seam yellow. \n．分布：歐洲南部，西起西班牙東北部和法國，東到土耳其。生活在丘陵的乾燥草原、灌叢、沙丘、岩石山坡地和海岸附近稀疏的樹林中。\nDistribution: It is native to the South Europe, ranging from as west as the Northeastern part of Spain and France, and as east as Turkey. It occurs to dry hilly grasslands, scrubs, sand dunes, and rocky slopes, and sparsely populated woodlands close to the coast.  \n</string>

    <string name="blank"></string>

    <string name="list_title">清單</string>
    <string name="home_title">Taipei Zoo</string>
    <string name="schedule_title">行程</string>

    <string name="fab_friend">好友位置</string>
    <string name="fab_route">行程清單</string>
    <string name="fab_clear">清理地圖</string>

</resources>
